{
    "name": "The Moon",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The Moon always shows Earth the same face?",
            "type": "tf",
            "correct": "True",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many days does it take for the Moon to orbit Earth?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "27.3 days",
            "answers": [
                "27.3 days",
                "It does not orbit Earth",
                "1 day",
                "365 days"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Moon phases are the same everywhere on Earth?",
            "type": "tf",
            "correct": "True",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is gravity like on the moon compared to Earth?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "1/6th Earths Gravity",
            "answers": [
                "1/6th Earths Gravity",
                "1/2 Earths Gravity",
                "Same As Earth",
                "1/4 Earths Gravity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The combination of Earthâ€™s gravity and the gravitational pull of the Moon creates what?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "Tidal force",
            "answers": [
                "Tidal force",
                "Dust",
                "Wind",
                "Moonlight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The Moon moderates Earths' climate by....",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "Moderating Earth's Wobble",
            "answers": [
                "Moderating Earth's Wobble",
                "Creating Sunlight",
                "Protecting Earth from Astroids",
                "FIlling the Atmosphere with Dust"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In Latin, the Moon was called what?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "Luna",
            "answers": [
                "Luna",
                "Starlink",
                "God",
                "Crateria"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What gives the Moons' Surface Static Electricity?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "Solar Wind",
            "answers": [
                "Solar Wind",
                "Rotation",
                "Earth",
                "Air"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The distance between the Moon and Earth is?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "238,900 Miles",
            "answers": [
                "238,900 Miles",
                "103,600 Miles",
                "31,730 Miles",
                "1,532,377 Miles"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In what year did humans walk on the Moon for the first time?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "1969",
            "answers": [
                "1969",
                "1973",
                "1970",
                "1958"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "id": 1707617566386
}